{"experimentVersion":"micro_debug","participantID":"Hannah","participantAge":"26","participantGender":1,"confirmationCode":"0605403","participantFeedback":"test","totalTrials":14,"dataRecordFrequency":0.03999999910593033,"restbreakDuration":5.0,"getReadyDuration":5.0,"trialList":[0,1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8,9,10,11,12,13],"allTrialData":[{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[0],"mapName":"Persistent","trialAnswer":"","trialQuestion":"","trialStimulus":"","trialPossibleAnswers":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.0,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":0.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"pausePriorFeedbackTime":0.30000001192092898,"feedbackFlashDuration":1.2000000476837159,"trialScore":0.0,"maxResponseTime":5.0,"responseTime":[0.0],"responseChoice":[""],"choiceCorrect":[false],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[false],"FLAG_trialError":[false]},{"trialNumber":1,"trialListIndex":[1],"mapName":"InformationScreen","trialAnswer":"","trialQuestion":"","trialStimulus":"","trialPossibleAnswers":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.0,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":0.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"pausePriorFeedbackTime":0.30000001192092898,"feedbackFlashDuration":1.2000000476837159,"trialScore":0.0,"maxResponseTime":5.0,"responseTime":[0.0],"responseChoice":[""],"choiceCorrect":[false],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[false],"FLAG_trialError":[false]},{"trialNumber":2,"trialListIndex":[2],"mapName":"BeforeStartingScreen","trialAnswer":"","trialQuestion":"","trialStimulus":"","trialPossibleAnswers":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.0,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":0.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"pausePriorFeedbackTime":0.30000001192092898,"feedbackFlashDuration":1.2000000476837159,"trialScore":0.0,"maxResponseTime":5.0,"responseTime":[0.0],"responseChoice":[""],"choiceCorrect":[false],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[false],"FLAG_trialError":[false]},{"trialNumber":3,"trialListIndex":[3],"mapName":"ConsentScreen","trialAnswer":"","trialQuestion":"","trialStimulus":"","trialPossibleAnswers":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.0,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":0.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"pausePriorFeedbackTime":0.30000001192092898,"feedbackFlashDuration":1.2000000476837159,"trialScore":0.0,"maxResponseTime":5.0,"responseTime":[0.0],"responseChoice":[""],"choiceCorrect":[false],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[false],"FLAG_trialError":[false]},{"trialNumber":4,"trialListIndex":[4],"mapName":"StartScreen","trialAnswer":"","trialQuestion":"","trialStimulus":"","trialPossibleAnswers":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.0,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":0.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"pausePriorFeedbackTime":0.30000001192092898,"feedbackFlashDuration":1.2000000476837159,"trialScore":0.0,"maxResponseTime":5.0,"responseTime":[0.0],"responseChoice":[""],"choiceCorrect":[false],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[false],"FLAG_trialError":[false]},{"trialNumber":5,"trialListIndex":[5],"mapName":"InstructionsScreen","trialAnswer":"","trialQuestion":"","trialStimulus":"","trialPossibleAnswers":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.0,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":0.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"pausePriorFeedbackTime":0.30000001192092898,"feedbackFlashDuration":1.2000000476837159,"trialScore":0.0,"maxResponseTime":5.0,"responseTime":[0.0],"responseChoice":[""],"choiceCorrect":[false],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[false],"FLAG_trialError":[false]},{"trialNumber":6,"trialListIndex":[6],"mapName":"Practice","trialAnswer":"Yes!","trialQuestion":"Is this new game really awesome?","trialStimulus":"questionIcon","trialPossibleAnswers":["Na it sucks","It's ok","Yes!"],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.0,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":0.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"pausePriorFeedbackTime":0.30000001192092898,"feedbackFlashDuration":1.2000000476837159,"trialScore":0.0,"maxResponseTime":5.0,"responseTime":[3.4167308807373049],"responseChoice":["Yes!"],"choiceCorrect":[true],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[false],"FLAG_trialError":[false]},{"trialNumber":7,"trialListIndex":[7],"mapName":"GetReady","trialAnswer":"","trialQuestion":"","trialStimulus":"","trialPossibleAnswers":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.0,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":0.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"pausePriorFeedbackTime":0.30000001192092898,"feedbackFlashDuration":1.2000000476837159,"trialScore":0.0,"maxResponseTime":5.0,"responseTime":[3.4167308807373049],"responseChoice":[""],"choiceCorrect":[false],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[false],"FLAG_trialError":[false]},{"trialNumber":8,"trialListIndex":[8],"mapName":"MainTrial","trialAnswer":"No","trialQuestion":"Is this a bird?","trialStimulus":"icecream","trialPossibleAnswers":["Yes","No"],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.0,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":0.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"pausePriorFeedbackTime":0.30000001192092898,"feedbackFlashDuration":1.2000000476837159,"trialScore":10.0,"maxResponseTime":5.0,"responseTime":[1.5339241027832032],"responseChoice":["No"],"choiceCorrect":[true],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[false],"FLAG_trialError":[false]},{"trialNumber":9,"trialListIndex":[9],"mapName":"MainTrial","trialAnswer":"Yes!","trialQuestion":"Is this new game really awesome?","trialStimulus":"questionIcon","trialPossibleAnswers":["Na it sucks","It's ok","Yes!"],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.0,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":0.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"pausePriorFeedbackTime":0.30000001192092898,"feedbackFlashDuration":1.2000000476837159,"trialScore":-5.0,"maxResponseTime":5.0,"responseTime":[0.9166793823242188],"responseChoice":["It's ok"],"choiceCorrect":[false],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[false],"FLAG_trialError":[false]},{"trialNumber":10,"trialListIndex":[10],"mapName":"MainTrial","trialAnswer":"Unclear","trialQuestion":"Is consuming this a good life choice?","trialStimulus":"wine","trialPossibleAnswers":["Unclear","No","Totally"],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.0,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":0.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"pausePriorFeedbackTime":0.30000001192092898,"feedbackFlashDuration":1.2000000476837159,"trialScore":10.0,"maxResponseTime":5.0,"responseTime":[0.7331199645996094],"responseChoice":["Unclear"],"choiceCorrect":[true],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[false],"FLAG_trialError":[false]},{"trialNumber":11,"trialListIndex":[11],"mapName":"MainTrial","trialAnswer":"Yes","trialQuestion":"Is this a cheese?","trialStimulus":"cheese","trialPossibleAnswers":["Yes","No"],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.0,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":0.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"pausePriorFeedbackTime":0.30000001192092898,"feedbackFlashDuration":1.2000000476837159,"trialScore":10.0,"maxResponseTime":5.0,"responseTime":[0.8838043212890625],"responseChoice":["Yes"],"choiceCorrect":[true],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[false],"FLAG_trialError":[false]},{"trialNumber":12,"trialListIndex":[12],"mapName":"MainTrial","trialAnswer":"Yes!","trialQuestion":"Is this new game really awesome?","trialStimulus":"questionIcon","trialPossibleAnswers":["Na it sucks","It's ok","Yes!"],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.0,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":0.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"pausePriorFeedbackTime":0.30000001192092898,"feedbackFlashDuration":1.2000000476837159,"trialScore":10.0,"maxResponseTime":5.0,"responseTime":[0.9002914428710938],"responseChoice":["Yes!"],"choiceCorrect":[true],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[false],"FLAG_trialError":[false]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"Exit","trialAnswer":"","trialQuestion":"","trialStimulus":"","trialPossibleAnswers":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.0,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":0.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"pausePriorFeedbackTime":0.30000001192092898,"feedbackFlashDuration":1.2000000476837159,"trialScore":0.0,"maxResponseTime":5.0,"responseTime":[],"responseChoice":[],"choiceCorrect":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[]}]}